Jack Goldring Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Jack Goldring Papers.
undated, 1940-1981.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Goldring, Jack.
1.3 linear feet.
Jacob (Jack) Goldring was born March 5, 1915 in Springfield, Massachusetts. Goldring's family moved to Hartford, Connecticut in 1928 when Jack was thirteen. Jack Goldring had a lengthy association with the Connecticut Communist party. After becoming a party member in 1936, he held many posts in the party's state apparatus; among them, Chairman of the Stanford Branch, 1938-1940; Chairman, G.E. Club, Bridgeport, 1946-1947; Fairfield County Chairman, 1947, 1952; and Legislative Director, 1954. In May of 1954, Goldring's communist affiliations led to his arrest by the F.B.I. Charged under the provisions of the Smith Act for pursuing subversive activities, his case was eventually dismissed on a technicality.
MSS19910037
Biography
Jacob Goldring (Jack) was born 5 March 1915 in Springfield, Massachusetts. Goldring's family moved to Hartford, Connecticut, in 1928 when Jack was thirteen. In 1932, he graduated from high school, and, unable to find steady employment, entered Central Connecticut College in 1934. Five months later, he enrolled in Connecticut State College in Storrs, where he participated in the R.O.T.C. program, and graduated in 1938 with a BS in math and social science. While a student, Goldring was also a member of the National Guard. In 1942, General Electric in Bridgeport, Connecticut, hired Goldring. In November of that year, he joined the Air Force, serving in the Pacific Theatre during World War II. He was honorably discharged in February 1946, and returned to G.E., where he was active in the union, serving as a shop steward from 1946-1947. In 1947, he left G.E. to assume a post in the Connecticut Communist Party.
Jack Goldring had a lengthy association with the Connecticut Communist Party. After becoming a party member in 1936, he held many posts in the party's state apparatus; among them, Chairman of the Stamford Branch, 1938-1940; Chairman, G.E. Club, Bridgeport, 1946-1947; Fairfield County Chairman, 1947, 1952; and Legislative Director, 1954.
In May of 1954, Goldring's communist affiliations led to his arrest by the F.B.I. Charged under the provisions of the Smith Act for pursuing subversive activities, his case was eventually dismissed on a technicality.
Scope and Content
The collection contains reports, surveys, and minutes, printed notices and bulletins, court documents and transcripts, newsclippings, union agreements, strike-related notices, and general information and articles pertaining to Goldring's activities. Appropriate brochures, pamphlets, and flyers have been removed from the collection and catalogued as indicated on the list below.
Arrangement
Series I: U.E./IUE Local 203 ( 1940-1970 ) contains materials concerned with the United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America Local 203, representing workers at the General Electric plant in Bridgeport, Connecticut. A small portion of this series deals with operational aspects of the union, including building associations, reports, surveys, and minutes. A majority of the series is in the form of printed notices and bulletins dealing with union issues and internal union elections. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject or type of material.
Series II: Smith Act Trial ( undated, 1954-1969 ) contains materials relevant to Goldring's 1954 trial for subversive activities, and includes court documents and transcripts, as well as materials issued by the Communist Party and the Connecticut Volunteers for Civil Rights. Also included in this series are newsclippings, reports, and biographical information on Goldring. The series is arranged alphabetically.
Series III: Newspaper Clippings and Subject Files ( 1944-1981 ) cover various political issues.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to labor in Connecticut. Communist Party materials may also be found in the Alternative Press Collection. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
16th Annual Convention, New England Regional Conference. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1954. (2 copies) Dodd Call No.
African Independent Movement: newsletter, flyers 1969-1970 Dodd Call No.
AIM, the American Independent Movement Newsletter, v. 2 February 1, 1970. Dodd Call No.
The American Standard of Living,undated Dodd Call No.
Connecticut Challenge,v. 1 #2 June 1954, v. 1 # 3 August 1954, v. 2 #2 May-June 1955, v, 2 #4 October 1955. Dodd Call No.
Daily World, The: articles, subscription material [1970] Dodd Call No.
Labor Today. [1968?] Dodd Call No.
Latin America Today. V. 4, #3-4, March -April 1954. Dodd Call No.
March of Labor, January 1956. Dodd Call No.
New Jersey Party Voice, September 1956. Dodd Call No.
New World Review. Subscription form. [1973?] Dodd Call No.
Party Affairs, v. 2 #3, 1968. Dodd Call No.
Party Voice, a Bulletin issued by the N.Y. State Communist Party, v. 2 #1, March 1954. Dodd Call No.
Pennsylvania Party Voice, v. I #2 August 1956 Dodd Call No.
Trade Unionist for Progressive Action. 1976 Dodd Call No.
U.E. News. 1944 Dodd Call No.
UE News, v. XXXIX #6, March 28, 1977. Dodd Call No.
The Union Speaks, v. 5 #3, March 1977. Dodd Call No.
“We Hold These Truths...”: Handbook for a Study of Constitutional Rights and Liberties, 1953. Dodd Call No.
Communist Party publications:
Bridgeport Club: “Red Wire” 1973-1976 Dodd Call No.
Columbia University Graduate School: “Graduate Scholar” 1937 Dec Dodd Call No.
Connecticut: “Connecticut Challenge” 1954-1955, 1959 Dodd Call No.
Illinois: “The Converyar” 1953 Jul-Aug Dodd Call No.
Illinois: “The Diesel Worker” 1953 Aug Dodd Call No.
Illinois: The Party Forum 1953 Oct Dodd Call No.
New York State 1954 Dodd Call No.
Norwalk branch: “Norwalk Neighbor” 1939 Jun Dodd Call No.
Stamford branch: “Stamford Worker” 1937-1938 Dodd Call No.
Stamford branch: “We The People” 1938-1940 Dodd Call No.
Stamford branch: “Yale and Town Workers” 1937 Apr-May Dodd Call No.
U.S.A., National Committee: “Party Affairs” 1959 Nov Dodd Call No.
U.S.A.: printed materials 1945-1982 Dodd Call No.
General Electric publications: Dodd Call No.
GE-IUE (AFL-CIO), national agreements 1952-1953, 1970-1973 Dodd Call No.
Communism in Unions 1952 Dodd Call No.
“News Magazine” 1973 Jun Dodd Call No.
Strike bulletins and information 1969-1970 Dodd Call No.
Notice of statutory meeting of share owners 1970 Mar Dodd Call No.
International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. IUE News. 1970 Feb. Dodd Call No.
Reporter. International Union of Mill, Mine and Smelter Workers. 1953 Dec Dodd Call No.
Lenin on the Jewish Question. New York: International Publishers, 1934. Dodd Call No.
Jenminjihpao, “Once More about the Historical Experience of the Dictatorship of the Prolketariat”, Moscow: Foreign Languages Publishing House, 1957. Dodd Call No.
The People vs. McCarthyism: The Case Against the McCarran Act, Abt, John: 1953. Dodd Call No.
A Union Statement on Civil Rights. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO undated Dodd Call No.
Agreement between A.C.C.C. Bridgeport Plant and The United Steelworkers of America. American Chain and Cable Company, Inc. 1965 October. Dodd Call No.
The Case Against the House Un-American Activities Committee. American Civil Liberties Union. Dodd Call No.
Yankee Toolmaker Abroad. American Committee to Survey Labor Conditions in Europe. 1951 Dodd Call No.
A Man... A Woman and G.E. American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, National Auxiliaries. undated Dodd Call No.
An open letter.. American Town Hall Federation. 1970 January Dodd Call No.
An open letter. Anti-aircraft conspiracy. 1970 Dodd Call No.
The Fraud of “Soviet Anti-Semitism”. Aptheker, Herbert. New York: New Century Publishers, 1962. Dodd Call No.
Bay Area Boycott G.E. Committee. 1972-1975 Dodd Call No.
Labor Radical, Beacon Press. order form, Lev DeCaux. 1971 Dodd Call No.
Economic Concentration and World War II. Report of the Smaller War Plants Coporation to the Special Committee to Study Problems of American Small Business. Blair, John M., et. al. Washington, D.C.: GPO, 1946. (Senate Doc. #206) Dodd Call No.
What to do about Communism in Union, Number 2 in the series, Statement before a Senate Subcommittee. Boulware, L.R., G.H. Pfeif and W.J. Barron. N.P.: General Electric, undated Dodd Call No.
Fund for the Social and Cultural Provisions of Workers, Trade Union Participation in Enterprise Planning. Central Council of Hungarian Trade Unions. undated Dodd Call No.
Freedom or Enforced Conformity. Chicago Committee to Defend Democratic Rights.[1960s] Dodd Call No.
The Naked Rise of Communism. Citizen's Anti-Communist Committee. undated Dodd Call No.
End McCarranism: On This We Stand Together. Citizen's Committee for Constitutional Liberties. 1962 Dodd Call No.
Mundt, Ferguson Nixon vs. America's Freedoms. Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts. 1950 Dodd Call No.
Clergy and Laymen Concerned about Vietnam. Flyer 1968 Dodd Call No.
Committee on Un-American Activities. 1953 Dodd Call No.
Let's Take a Second Look.... Committee to End Sedition undated Dodd Call No.
Connecticut and the 1954 elections. Communist Party of Connecticut. Bridgeport, CT: Communist Party of Connecticut, 1954. (8 copies) Dodd Call No.
The Economy of Connecticut: Problems and Program. Communist Party of Connecticut. Bridgeport, CT: Communist Party of Connectcut, 1958. Dodd Call No.
Flood Rehabilitation Program for Connecticut. Communist Party of Connecticut. Bridgeport, CT: Communist Party of Connecticut, undated (13 copies) Dodd Call No.
The American Way to Jobs, Peace, Dodd Call No.
Democracy: Draft Program of the Communist Party. Communist Party of the United States of America. New York: New Century Publishers, March 1954. (2 copies) Dodd Call No.
The American Way to Jobs, Peace, Democracy: Draft Program of the Communist Party. Communist Party of the United States of America. New York: New Century Publishers, April 1954. (3 copies) Dodd Call No.
Communist Election Paltform 1938. Communist Party of the United States of America. New York: Connecticut State Committee, Communist Party of the United States of America, 1938. (2 copies) Dodd Call No.
Constitution of the Communist Party of the United States of America. Communist Party of the United States of America. New York: The Communist Party, U.S.A., 1948. (2 copies) Dodd Call No.
New Program of the Communist Party U.S.A. Communist Party of the United States of America. (Second Draft). New York: Communist Party, U.S.A., 1968. Dodd Call No.
Congress of Industrial Organization (C.I.O.). Political pamphlets. 1942-1944 Dodd Call No.
Connecticut Commission Against Inflation and Unemployment. Political petition. undated Dodd Call No.
The Connecticut Unemployment Compensation Law. Connecticut Labor Department. 1967 Dodd Call No.
Connecticut Needs Peace. Connecticut Peace Council. undated Dodd Call No.
Connecticut State Building Trades Welfare and Insurance Fund. Benefits pamphlet. 1968 Dodd Call No.
State-wide Pension Fund. Connecticut State Council of Carpenters. 1967 Dodd Call No.
Constitution of the Connecticut State industrial Union Council CIO. Connecticut State Industrial Union. New Haven, CT: Connecticut State Industrial Union, 1952. Dodd Call No.
Call to action. Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO. Dodd Call No.
First Official Yearbook. Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO. 1957 Dodd Call No.
Connecticut Volunteers for Civil Rights. Political flyers. 1955 Dodd Call No.
Report from Connecticut. Connecticut Volunteers for Civil Rights. 1955-1956 Dodd Call No.
Reporter. Connecticut Volunteers for Civil Rights. 1955-1956 Dodd Call No.
An Historic Contribution In Defense of the Constitution of the United States. Connecticut Volunteers for Civil Rights. New Haven, CT: Connecticut Volunteers for Civil Rights, undated (2 copies) Dodd Call No.
Second Front Menace. Cronin, John F. 1943 Dodd Call No.
The Rape of the First Amendment. Crosby, Alexander. 962 Dodd Call No.
Why I am a Communist. Davis, Benjamin. New York: New Century Publishers, 1947. Dodd Call No.
The Communists Take a New Look: Report to the National Committee of the Communist Party, U.S.A. Dennis, Eugene. New York: New Century Publishers, 1956. Dodd Call No.
Drug and Hospital News. Drug and Hospital Union, R.W.D.S.U./ AFL-CIO, Local 1199. 1969 November. Dodd Call No.
Emergency Civil Liberties Committee. 1945-1965. Dodd Call No.
The Glass Onion. Fairfield High School Students. 1970. Dodd Call No.
Fishman, Joelle. Campaign flyers and buttons. 1975. Dodd Call No.
The Fight for Unity in Connecticut and the Struggles Ahead. Fishman, Joelle. 1979 Dodd Call No.
Beware of the War Danger! Stop Look and Listen! New York: New Century Publishers, 1948. Dodd Call No.
A Letter to Presbyterians Concerning the present Situation in Our Country and in the World. General Assembly of the Presbyterian Church. Foster, William Z. Philadelphia, Office of the General Assembly, 1953. Dodd Call No.
The Rights Yu Save may be Your Own. Gerson, Simon W. New York: New York State Communist Party, Dodd Call No.undated
The Eleventh Hour: Defeat the New Facist Threat. Hall, Gus. 1964. Dodd Call No.
Where It's At: A Research Guide for Communist Organizations. Hamburg, Jill. 1967. Dodd Call No.
Democracy, Civil Rights, and Liberty in Connecticut. Howard, Daniel. 1958. Dodd Call No.
Democracy, Civil Rights andliberty in Connecticut. Howard, Daniel. Windsor, CT: Daniel Howard, undated Dodd Call No.
McCarthyism and the Big Lie. Howard, Milton. 1953. Dodd Call No.
Independent party. Flyers. 1975-1979 Dodd Call No.
Unemployment and the Machine. Industrial Workers of the World. 1934. Dodd Call No.
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 609. Union pamphlet. 1976 Dodd Call No.
International publishers. Catalogs. 1971. Dodd Call No.
International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO. Flyers regarding G.E. 1951-1954. Dodd Call No.
International Union of Mill, Mine and Smelter Workers, Local 552. Strike bulletins. undated Dodd Call No.
Constitution of the International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. International Union of the United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW-CIO). 1953. Dodd Call No.
Jefferson School of Social Science. Marxist study guides. undated Dodd Call No.
What Can I Do. Join Hands. undated Dodd Call No.
Bolshevik. # 23, 1953. Dodd Call No.
Labor Education Fund. Pamphlets. [1974?] Dodd Call No.
Labor and Peace. Labor Research Associates. Kuzminov, I. “The Crisis Character of the Economic Development of the U.S.A. in the Post-War Period”, 1966. Dodd Call No.
Voting Records of Senators and Representatives 1947 through 1952. Labor's Leaguefor Political Education. Washington, D.C. Labor's League for Political Education, undated Dodd Call No.
Palante. Latin Revolutionary News Service. 1970 July. Dodd Call No.
This is a Weapon. Legislative Committee of the Westside Parent-Teacher Association. Middletown, CT: Westside PTA, undated Dodd Call No.
Lithuanian Committee to Combat Nazism and Facism. 1964 Dodd Call No.
The Promise of Automation and how to Realize it. Lumer, Hyman. New York: New Century Publishers, 1956. Dodd Call No.
McCarthy, Eugene. “McCarthy for President”. 1968. Dodd Call No.
Institutional Racism In American Society: A Primer. Mid-Peninsula Christian Ministry. 1968. Dodd Call No.
Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U. Mikoyan, A.I. Moscow: Foreign Languages Publishing House, 1956. Dodd Call No.
Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U. Molotov, V.M. Moscow: Foreign Languages Publishing House, 1956. Dodd Call No.
The Roots and Prospects of McCarthyism. Monthly Review. 1954. Dodd Call No.
Congressional Record. Morton, Honorable Thurston. “Speech”. 1967 December. Dodd Call No.
What You Need to Know About the McCarran Act. National Committee for the Repeal of the McCarran Act. [1964?] Dodd Call No.
National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee. 1964-1966. Dodd Call No.
National Committee to Support General Electric Strikers. 1969-1970. Dodd Call No.
Can Americans Tolerate Prison for Ideas? National Committee to Win Amnesty for the Smith Act Prisoners.1954. Dodd Call No.
1952 Election Paltform of the Communist Party. National Election Campaign Committee of the Communist Party. New York: Election Campaign Committee of the Communist Party, 1952. Dodd Call No.
National Football League. 1969.
Mandel vs. McCarthy. National Guardian. 1953. Dodd Call No.
Let Freedom Ride the Rails. National Negro Labor Council. 1954. Dodd Call No.
National Rank and File Conference, Arrangements Committee. Flyer. 1970 Dodd Call No.
Manual of Instructions and Temporary Rules. National Union for Social Justice. 1935. Dodd Call No.
New Haven Peoples Center. 1979. Dodd Call No.
Two Roads. Palmer, Milton. Philadelphia: North Club and the Section Committee of the 1st Congressional District, 1958. Dodd Call No.
People's Party of Connecticut. 1948, 1952. Dodd Call No.
Progressive Party.
McCarthyism in the Courts: The Story of the Steve Nelson Frame Up. Provisional Committee to Free Steve Nelson. 1953. Dodd Call No.
Resolution on the Jewish Question. Provisional Organizaing Committee for a Communist Party. 1958. Dodd Call No.
Puerto-Rico Parade of Connecticut, Inc. Flyer. undated Dodd Call No.
The Nation (reprint), June 6, 1953. Dodd Call No.
Ribicoff, Senator Abe. 1975-1976. Dodd Call No.
How to De-Control Your Union of Communists. Rice, Rev. Charles Owen. Redlich, Norman and Laurent B. Frantz. “Does Silence Mean Guilt? The Fifth Amendment Controversy,” undated Dodd Call No.
S.A.N.E./A Citizen's Organization for a Sane World, Inc. 1968-1969. Dodd Call No.
This Thing Called Profits. Schauble, Peter. 1952. Dodd Call No.
State Industrial Union Council. 1944. Dodd Call No.
Minority Group Integration by Labor and Management, A Study of the Employment Practices of the larger Employers, and the Membership Practices of the Larger Labor Unions with Respect to Race, Religion, and National Origin. Stetler, Henry G. Hartford, CT: Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, 1953. Dodd Call No.
Student Groups. undated Dodd Call No.
History of May Day. Trachtenberg, Alexander. New York: International Publishers, 1947. Dodd Call No.
The Devil in the Book, The Time of the Toad. Trumbo, Dalton. 1956. Dodd Call No.
United Auto Workers (UAW). Political and union-related pamphlets. 1942-1955. Dodd Call No.
Washington Report: Walter Reuther, 1907-70. United Auto Workers (UAW). 1970. Dodd Call No.
Community Action Programs Council. United Auto Workers (UAW). 1970-1971. Dodd Call No.
The Kohler Worker's Story. United Auto Workers (UAW). Local 833: 1954. Dodd Call No.
United Auto Workers (UAW). Local 1010: strike announcements. 1970. Dodd Call No.
United Auto Workers (UAW). Local 1012: union bulletin. undated Dodd Call No.
A Dog-Tag for Labor! New York: United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, undated Dodd Call No.
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Agreement between G.E. and U.E. 1943-1948 Dodd Call No.
Eyes on Washington. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America.(UE). 1957 May. Dodd Call No.
The Mundt Control Bill: A Law to Gag the American People. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. 1948. Dodd Call No.
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Printed materials. 1942-1984. Dodd Call No.
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Suggested sample constitution.1944. Dodd Call No.
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. 37th National Convention report 1980. (2 folders) Dodd Call No.
On the Beam. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Local 203. 1944-1946. Dodd Call No.
Local 209 News. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Local 209. 1954 March. Dodd Call No.
Boycott Grapes. United Farm Workers Committee. undated Dodd Call No.
United Mine Workers of America, Local 12083. [1939?] Dodd Call No.
United States Commission on Civil Rights. 1968-1969. Dodd Call No.
United Steelworkers of America. Local 7528. undated Dodd Call No.
Labor and Haymarket Scrapbook, 1873-1919. United Steelworkers of America. 1873-1919. Dodd Call No.
Report on agreement with U.S.X. Corp. United Steelworkers of America. 1978. Dodd Call No.
United Steelworkers of America. Labor history. undated Dodd Call No.
Red Pipe Line into Our Defense Plants. Velre, Lester. undated Dodd Call No.
Jobs Galore after the War. Vernon, J. 1943. Dodd Call No.
Notes on the Foreign Situation Based on a Trip Abroad. Weir, Ernest T. Pittsburgh, PA: Ernest T. Weir, 1953. Dodd Call No.
the People versus Segregated Schools. Wilkerson, Doxey A. New York: New Century Publishers, 1955. Dodd Call No.
Wards by Words. Woods, J.B.C. 1970 April. Dodd Call No.
World Fellowship, Inc. [1955?] Dodd Call No.
When Peace Comes? undated Dodd Call No.
Schick Worker. Young Communist League. Y.W.C.A. National Board. 1937. Dodd Call No.
Young Workers Liberation League. undated Dodd Call No.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
Communist Party of the United States of America. Connecticut.; United States. Alien registration act, 1940.; Trials (Sedition)—Connecticut.; Communists—Connecticut.; Connecticut—Politics and government—1951-; Connecticut—Politics and government—1865-1950.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Personal Papers.; Newspaper Clippings.; Publications.
Occupations:
Labor leader.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Custodial History
The Jack Goldring papers were given by Goldring to Bruce Stave of the University of Connecticut History Department.
Acquisition Information
Professor Stave transferred the papers to the Historical Manuscripts and Archives Department (now Archives & Special Collections) of the University Libraries in July 1991.
Detailed Description
- Series I: U.E./IUE Local 203, undated, 1940-1970
  - Building Association notes and reports, undated (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Business agent controversy: flyers and notes, 1945-1946 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - District 2 Executive Board, UERMWA: correspondence, minutes, notices, ca. 1940 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Department newsletters, undated (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Drafts of constitution and by-laws, [1945?] (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Expulsion issue: flyers and notes, 1945-1947 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Financial records and receipts, 1941-1954 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - General Electric bulletins, ca. 1940s (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Grievance materials and reports, ca. 1940s (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Independent Committee for Unity of G.E. Local 203, UE-CIO; “Victory through Unity”, 1944 November 3 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: application card, undated (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Notes, undated (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Reports and surveys, undated (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Resolution on communism, 1945 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Strike bulletins, 1946-1970 (Box 1:, Folder 17-18)
  - Union bulletins, 1945-1974 (Box 1:, Folder 19-21)
  - Union elections
    - Berescik/Julianelle, 1946 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
    - Campaign flyers, 1940-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 23-26)
  - Union history, 1936-1938 (Box 1:, Folder 27)
- Series II: Smith Act Trial, undated, 1954-1969
  - Communist Party of Connecticut: press releases, public statements, party agendas, 1954-1969 (Box 1:, Folder 28)